HanOlly.exe + HanOlly.dll - [Themida 1.9.5.0]

- This is a custom Olly and Plugin that defeats Themida 1.9.5.0 Anti-Debugger checks (tested with Shooo's unpackme).
- Olly is modified the least amount possible, only bypasses debugger checks, and nothing more, very close to orgional "clean" olly.
- The plugin also works with OllyIce but I dont know exactly what has been modified in OllyIce so I cannot guarentee it is stable.

- 这是一个定制olly和插件这败仗t hemida1 .9.5.0反调试检查（检验shooo的unpackme） 。 
- olly是修饰最可能的，只有绕道调试检查，并没有什么更多的，非常接近orgional"干净"的olly。 
- 插件也能与ollyice但我dont确切地知道哪些已经修改ollyice所以我不能保证它是稳定的

- This is designed for Windows XP, this will not work for ANYTHING except XP.
- Do not use HideToolz when you use this, it might cause "Blue Screen Of Death"
-这是专为windowsx p的，这将是行不通的事，除了xp的。 
-不要使用hidetoolz当您使用这一点，很可能导致"蓝色屏幕上的死亡"


I want to say thank you to Shooo for posting the unpackme, its very hard to find a Themida 1.9.5.0 application  
Thank you to all of the Chinese unpacking community for providing so many resources, especially to someone who dosent speak english like me.  

If there are any problems are bugs that you find in this, please post in this thread so that I can make a patch and update it ^^.