Foreword

	 When NonaWrite comes out, but also really thought later will write the patch code in OD is a quite crisp matter, but will write is writing, the discovery will not be feeling well,
When has very jumps transfers, changes painfully, worst case scenario changes a place, possible all to jump transfers all must change.The chief criminal on does not have the marking
The function, this also is SkyPatch must realize.
　

　　
First, installment
Put SkyPatch.dll in the OllyDBG plug-in folder, put RAEdit.dll in the OllyDBG root directory.
(Note:RAEdit.dll cannot be put in the plug-in folder, otherwise OD will think it is also a plug-in, like you would install NonaWrite, also please first plug-in item
Takes down RAEdit.dll to transfer to root folder, actually NonaWrite as useless as RAEdit.dll).


Second, use
	 SkyPatch is one brand-new, with NonaWrite similar, use to help you to write the patch code in OllyDbg the plug-in unit, had it, this returns
         You can discover really writes the patch code in OD is a quite crisp matter.
	 The GUI is quite simple,
	 A code edit window, borrows KetilO (the RadASM author) RAEdit controls (to thank extremely)
	 An information output window
	 Four pressed keys, realize the assembly patch code separately, opens the script file (extension named .odp or .txt),Save script, Close the main GUI window
	 Was left over is you writes the script the matter, but before writing, please take a look at the example script, test1.odp


Third, grammar
	 Supports all can assemble the order in OllyDbg “which in the " window inputs, and increased the marking and the block annotation function.
===============================================================================
	 Marking
	 The marking cannot the duplicate, divide into following several kinds

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

	 General marking
	 example:@xxx:
	 Explanation:By “@” start, “:But” ending, middle free 26 letters and digital combination
	 Reference:
@loop3:  
  xor ecx, ecx

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

	 String marking
	 example:$xxx 
	 Explanation:But by “@” start, blank space “” ending, middle free 26 letters and digital combination,
	 　　　Behind the string marking may with use the string of character which “” causes, after the translation to be able automatically in the string add-on 0, or
	 　　　With the hexadecimal system string of character which # # causes, the size must be multiples of 2
	 　　　The string marking may quote in the code
	 Reference:
$str1 “this is the first string”   
		 “jjjs this is the first string”
$str2 # 45efe3003455667898df2256009980000 #

mov esi, $str2;Quotes the string marking in the code
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

	 Sentence conclusion marking
	 Form:@$xxx:
	 Explanation:By “@$” start, “:But” ending, middle free 26 letters and digital combination
	       After this marking just started only to want to use in the string block marking the string block conclusion address, behind discovered sometimes
	       After sentence also useful
	 Reference:
@0x00405E64:
	 jmp @start;Jumps out from 0x00405E64
@$backinit:   ;Again on the rebound time jumps out next place

@0x00402690:　;EIP marking, marking string block start
$str1 “this is the first string”    
		 “jjjs this is the first string”
$str2 # 45efe3003455667898df2256009980000 #
@$: ;Sentence conclusion marking, marking string block conclusion

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

	 EIP marking
	 Form:@0xxxx:
	 　　　The EIP marking = sentence conclusion marking ± hexadecimal system constant (front contains the 0x prefix):
	 Explanation:Two ways of eip marking, one, by “@0x” start, “:But” ending, middle free hexadecimal system address
	 　　　Second, the EIP marking by “@” the start, including the free 26 letters and digital combination marking, “=” behind is one
	 　　　An expression (the sentence conclusion marking [add or minus] a hexadecimal system constant), finally by “:” Ending
	 Reference:
@0x00402690:　;EIP marking, marking string block start
$str1 “this is the first string”    
		 “jjjs this is the first string”
$str2 # 45efe3003455667898df2256009980000 #
@$:           ;Sentence conclusion marking, marking string block conclusion

@start = @$ + 0x4:   ;Is separated by 4 bytes with the string block conclusion to start to write the code
call 406210

================================================================================
	 The annotation, divides into the specific annotation and the block annotation
	 
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

	 Specific annotation
	 Form:;xxxxxxxx
	 Explanation:By “;” Starts to mark, may pour an entire line or follow after the code

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

	 Block annotation
	 Form:/* xxxxxxx */
	 Explanation:By “/*” starts to mark, by “*/” conclusion marking

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Fourth, an example
	 Sees also a package of center the test1.odp patch script
	 
Fifth, thanks
	 Thanks olly to develop the such good tool, tries item to wait for 2.0 arrivals
	 Thanks KetilO (the RadASM author) RAEdit controls (to thank extremely)

Finally, so the plug-in unit can have the help to you, then my goal has achieved, also hoped sincerely each proposes the valued suggestion


Author: exfksy
Contact method:exfksy@163.com
Finishes the date:2006.12.10
